It's about 12:00 noon at the Murakata Yuriks, the second day of the Murakata Festival 2023.
Isn't it big?
I'm not underestimating Murakata.
I had my coming-of-age ceremony at Yuriks.
Since the Showa era... It doesn't matter since the Showa era.
It's for everyone. It's for everyone.
And here... we always came to the planetarium when we were students.
You were here on a date... alone.
I'm going to the festival now.
I'm going to the live one.
Have you seen it?
No, not live.
It's my first time.
Of course there's a video.
I've seen them on location.
But those fluffy girls...
Can they do it? Live?
They're so graceful.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
They do that, don't they?
The Yo-Ka-Yo Ka Dance is...
As for Dragon Ball...
That's where we started, right?
I took the liberty of making a video of it.
The Yo-kai-yo-ka Dance?
Yes, we did.
By the way, the fan's fault is...
Mr. Thanh.
That's so cool!
Thank you very much.
Boo hoo! They're all robots! I got these for you... from Placechan.
I got this one from Placechan, and it's got four of them, and it really does work, Batten Girl, so it's got a color.
I can't tell if there's a battery in it or not.
I don't know how to turn it on.
This way?
I think it's this way.
It's this way.
No, it's not.
Here it is.
Just hold it this way.
This one's a little tricky, changing colors.
I don't know... whose color is this?
Here we go.
Let's go with the one that's the least anyone's color.
That's it!
It's going to be "chancha"!
Let's go!
The end.
If it's not there, you're just gonna open it?
It's going to happen pretty soon.
Wow, I can't do it.
I really can't.
Are you okay?
You want to go?
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to cut you off again.
Would you mind starting with me?
I've never been here before.
Really?
You're dancing like crazy.
I've never seen you before.
It's fate that our eyes met.
I wish I could dream like this.
I don't care if I want to.
I don't care
I don't remember it I'm chasing it
In between
I know now
We've crossed paths
Love
Let's go in space
We'll meet again
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the rehearsal. I look forward to working with you halfway through.
What? Rehearsal?
What's rehearsing?
If there's air in the room, it's a rehearsal?
If there's air in the room, it's a rehearsal? It was like that.
I thought it was going to be over in a huff.
It's like Kyushu.
So it's a rehearsal.
So this is how you get things going?
That's embarrassing.
I feel like I've been cheated.
I was so excited that the show had started, but now I'm embarrassed.
Seriously.
Just like that?
I was impressed, though.
Oh yeah, for the first time.
I did think it was a little fluffy.
Overall.
I see. That's for sure.
Oh, seriously.
But, well, it was good.
So you can see it from the show.
Yes, yes.
No, no, no.
Yay.
Yes!
Why not?
It's a Google channel.
Please check it out!
Let's support them together!
That's enough.
You're here, too.
That's for sure.
It's a big indoor venue.
Seriously, it's like a regular 10-minute show.
Even if you're a Bus Chou-Chan fan.
If there are people who don't know each other...
I don't think I'd be able to handle it.
That's for sure.
Now, Murakata Setsusha 2023.
And now, here they come!
The Mattei Shoujo-tai!
Let's have a big round of applause.
Let's hear it.
Let's go!
Thank you for waiting.
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle!
Thank you for watching!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
under the bright red see of the universe shikatarikimodram
Oh, oh, oh, two people stop, badass badass
If you wake up in the morning and dance, you will be overflowing with energy
Bishonen Yume Sometimes Nonkenpon
Oisa oisa oisa oisa oisa
Those days
I want to burst, I can't burst, you're not enough
I want to burst I can't do it I want to leave you
I want to burst I can't burst you're not enough
I want to burst I can't stand it I want to leave you
I can't stop holding on to you
I'm in real love. I'm in real love.
See,야... If you float away, then...
I'm in love. I'm in love.
See, Hah! You'll fall in love.
See, Hah! If you float on the water...
I'm in love. I'm in love.
See, Hah! If you wear out your breath
Because you'll disappear there.
I'm skeptical.
Thank you for watching.
Come on, come on, come on
Even though life was lit
Now it's more than just sky, sandy beaches and parks
People passing by, waiting for love
Monsters and ghosts are also in a frenzy
Still following an unknown destiny
Every time I dream, a balloon pops and pops
Yeah!
I can't see it, I can't end it yet
Chasing after love, I can't reach it
Tightening paint, drying sweat, stop stepping, remake after remake
Even if you think it's okay to leave it like this
Feeling summer night, it's not over yet
I can't reach the love I'm chasing after
Cars passing each other, you loved me
The heart that goes on and on, from now on, ah, forever
I don't have to do my homework
I'm in love with you like stepping on a step
The chain came off and we pushed through
No more distance, I erased the map
Yeah!
I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it
I can't reach the love I'm chasing after
the tightening paint, the drying sweat, the stomping stop, the remake after
Even if you think it's okay to leave it like this
Feeling summer night, it's not over yet
I can't reach the love I'm chasing after
Cars passing each other, you loved me
The heart that goes on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on
Studio, stage.
I'm off!
Thank you very much.
Hello to all of you who have come to the stage from the countryside.
It's bartending time.
Hallo! I'm Kiyama from Ste.
I am Yuna Shukuyama.
I'm Rio Edo.
I am Kika Okada.
I am Ara Ooi.
I am Kiyama.
I'm Kiyama.
Can I write this girl?
Can I write about her?
It's okay to write.
Thank you very much.
Can I write about her?
It'll be like, "Who recommended this girl?
I'm nervous.
Thank you very much.
We at Bar Tension are active in Fukuoka, Kyushu,
We are the tourism ambassadors of Nakata City in Fukuoka.
Thank you very much.
The song that you all danced to earlier is called "Kono Minato" (This Port),
It is called "Kono Minato" (This Port),
Isn't there going to be fireworks at the end of the song?
To the tune of "This Port,
I see.
I'm filming it now, so please take a look if you like.
The fireworks above will be the last one to go off?
Yes.
Now, I would like to make this song a national tourism peace.
I hope you all dance with me,
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the next song.
Okay?
A.I.C. Words and music by Miho Nakajima Arranged by Miho Nakajima
A.I.C. Words and music by Miho Nakashima
A.I.C. lyrics and music by Miho Nakashima
I'm not clad in red halovinis
I'm like a person who's excited
What's that? What is it? I'm tired of breathing, I want to go back inside
I'm tired of breathing. I want to go back inside.
Pray for me.
A future to hold on to.
Chasing and swaying...
Two hands
Patten, patten, patten, I'm borrowing
Patten, Patten, Patten
A little last
borrowing
Patten, patten, patten, borrow
Let's go!
Let's go, bonbon nuts
Air batten
Tanpanpan Tattai On
Narase bonbon nunchi
Let it go, Gongon Nuts
Let's go for it!
You're taking it easy!
I'm not dreaming.
I'm not giving up.
You can't fight it. You can't fight it.
We don't have to stay here.
We're not giving up. We're not giving up. We're not giving up.
They've heard it a thousand times.
I've done it too many times.
And this world won't stop.
I can't stop until I'm beyond you
I don't want to look anywhere in hope
The first, the best.
The best, the best, the best.
The best, the best, the best, the best
The best, the best, the best, the best.
The Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best
The Best of the Best of the Best of the Best of the Best
The best of the best
The best of the best of the best of the best
The Best The Best The Best The Best
The Best of the Best Ward
This is the part where I wear your uding
H charm
I want to be loved
nime
Yes, I want to be loved. Let's go on the club stage together.
The sky of Cataluccia, the colors that fill
Magnificent view of the earth in Tottori
Mars in Kanagawa River of rivers
Expectations that swell above the time of year Expectations that look up
Look, from the horizon to the horizon Riding a good wind
Kyushu winter, Oki, a dream, a tiny dream, all aboard
Come on, let's find the story that hasn't started yet
Balloons on the surface of the water Promises llamas and
Orange sky, natural snow
Overlap this thought
Blue sky on the surface of the water A small future
A message of innocence, a taste of the future.
Riding in the shadows, I bind them with my hands
The bird sings, the bird plays...
I'm sorry, but what I'm looking for is a sentiment I can get attached to.
I'm looking for the sentiment that will get me through the night.
I'm looking for the high voice that jumps on the high voice, and I'm not even looking for the limit.
♪ Tonton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton.
Let's go find it
Oh oh oh oh
Let me dance, let me dance, let me dance some more
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh Oh Oh
Shine
Come to the busts, ladies and gentlemen
Let's make an S together
Right hand up, left hand down
I love it!
And the mu of the breast shape.
Right hand up, left hand down.
Thank you.
Ride that wind
On the beat of this hand raised
Into the sky.
Excuse me from the top. Where you can find what you're looking for.
Let's go find it.
Thank you.
Walk with me.
Yes.
It's the last part.
Let's go to the last part.
Let's get excited and go.
Let's get excited.
Let's go!
Ready.
Come on!
Se-no.
Yes, yes, yes!
Thank you very much.
Did you all have a good time?
It's going to be fun!
Today's stage has just begun,
We hope you will enjoy the Monacata Festival until the end.
We, the Battension Girls, will be on stage again tomorrow,
Please come and join us again,
It's a little bit different, isn't it?
Different?
I think so, so please come and see us.
Please come and see us.
And now, the two of us, the two batteresses,
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Have fun at the Monacata festival.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Thanks.
Gorgeous treasure, man!
Well, it was wonderful.
It was amazing!
You know what, she's cute!
So cute! And not cool!
And there's cool, and there's everything.
It was so beautiful!
I knew the stage was giving 120%, from the usual demureness.
It wasn't there.
I was so energetic!
I almost cried.
A little bit.
It was the first time for me to see it, and I was really moved.
I'm glad I saw it.
No, this is not important for Fukuoka?
No, it is. It's a treasure.
Yes, so you had a lot of fun at the Murakata festival.
Harmony Ball, right?
Oh, I see.
It's a separate place from the other live performance venue.
Separate, so this is where I saw the play.
They're having the company ceremony here?
Yes, the troupe ceremony and a place called, how do you say, Red Beard,
Redbeard.
You know, the doctor's, you know, that one?
That's where I saw the stage.
Wow.
Yeah, the music. And the Naked King, what's his name?
The Naked King.
It was in junior high, so I kind of forgot.
It was junior high school, so it was about 10 years ago.
Around the '70s.
Seventies.
Yes, it brings back memories. Maybe this part hasn't changed.
This place hasn't changed.
No, again, it was amazing, live.
It was amazing.
Seeing it live.
It was amazing. I was surprised.
I knew she was pretty.
And I knew she was a good singer,
I really didn't expect her to be that cool,
It was more than I expected.
It really was a team effort, a live performance.
I'm going to call you Basho, but I'm going to call you Basho-senpai.
Basho-sama.
Sama? It's "Sama-sama," right?
No, I heard that I can say hello behind the scenes.
Really?
It's a little different from before, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm a little nervous.
This is nice, a privilege.
When you become a fan, it's a privilege.
Of course I knew that,
I'm nervous when I think again that I'm an artist.
Oh, hey, hi.
Oh, hey.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
No, I saw you.
It's real.
Wow, I'm a little nervous.
Nervous, nervous.
No, no, no, you are an artist once again,
I'll remember it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, everyone.
Thank you very, very much.
I don't think of myself as an idol,
I feel like an artist,
I really like the way she looks.
She was so cute.
It was so cute.
Thank you very much.
And he was cool.
He was cool.
Non-stop A, right?
Yes, it was.
Five or six songs?
Six songs.
But how many more songs for a one-man show?
Yes, close to 20 songs.
Twenty songs.
I'm going to do a lot of colors.
Ten songs?
You mean you play that many songs in a row without a break?
We usually do as many songs as we can,
We want to play as many songs as possible,
So we want to be a little tight like that.
It's a lot of spinning, isn't it?
It was spinning.
And then the next one,
I can't see.
I said, "No, it's not good.
It's not okay.
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
I'm not talking so much,
I'm dancing and singing.
Yes, that's right.
She's pretty good.
He is good.
Also, I was surprised to see that he also incites the audience.
Yes, he does.
It's really something like this,
There are many choreographies that you can dance together with the audience,
I hope you will dance along with them.
That's for sure.
And the ones that the audience remembered,
Like that one with the parts.
That's right, making parts and so on.
This is this evening,
You sing what you're looking for?
How was it? They saw me.
I thought maybe you could do it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought maybe you could do the "S" in "S" or something.
I thought I could do it.
I was like, "Oh my God, I'm going to do it.
Like that, like that.
Like that.
Like limb shoulders.
I have a little stiffness in my shoulders.
Is that enough?
Yes, it is.
It's like a great rhythm.
Tight, tight, tight, tight, tight.
Can't you do something like this?
We can do it together,
We all dance and have fun.
I think it's all about the groove.
With a sense of enjoyment.
I see.
And tomorrow is the big day, right? Fireworks.
Yes, fireworks. Fireworks.
We'll do it to the tune of "Kono Port," right?
There's a song called "Kono Port.
You laughed, didn't you?
Kono Port is the name of the song,
That's why,
It's my hometown,
Kono Port! You know?
The rainbow one.
Oh, I see.
I see. Well done.
This is also as a breast shoulder,
Rinne-san wrote it for me,
When I listen to the lyrics,
I think it's perfect for chest-shoulders.
Many people with chest shoulders are geniuses.
We are geniuses. We are.
But if you look at O-chan, it's hard to call her a genius.
Is that so?
No, no, no, if you saw what you just saw,
Ai.
What are you talking about?
Ai, the senior with the chest and shoulders.
Again, what's wrong?
The gymnasium, you see.
When we went to see it,
It was a big gymnasium, right?
How was it to perform live there again?
It was like a real live music club,
The lights were really bright,
I didn't know it was possible to create such an atmosphere.
The atmosphere was amazing.
There really were a lot of people there,
There were a lot of fans in the audience.
It looked totally different from the last time I was there.
It was totally different from the last time I went.
It was totally different.
Before the show started, the fans were really enthusiastic.
Wow! Really?
They were curled up.
They were doing it, they were doing it.
When they were with us.
I interrupted him.
When he came in,
I said, "I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Like a rehearsal.
He said it was in front of the audience.
The festival is in front of the audience.
The time is a little fuzzy.
What do you think? Is there anything like this indoor festival?
It's rare to have so many different artists.
But it's so hot and exciting,
I thought it would be nice to have it indoors.
Yes, it was.
The atmosphere of the lighting was great.
The atmosphere was different between the live performance and the video on the screen.
It's a different atmosphere.
And I'm sure I'll be there tomorrow, too.
Yukima-chan, I would like to change the atmosphere a little tomorrow with the MC.
Tomorrow, it won't be just the six of us.
What?
You can do it?
One day.
That's crazy!
A day? I couldn't swim because there's no way I'm going swimming.
We invited DJ Park Goroku to join us.
Remixes only for this time.
Tomorrow only?
We also changed the song and remixed it.
Oh, wow.
A little surprise for the audience?
Yes, I guess so. We haven't done it at all.
It's sad.
There is an aroma.
Tomorrow is really non-stop.
Really? No more talking?
There is a little bit.
More nonstop?
Much more nonstop.
Like fast forward.
The DJ is already there.
Yes, that's right.
Well, now that you can hear us, maybe we can take a commemorative photo in front of you.
How much is it? How much do I have to pay?
Please decide.
There are five of us.
It's expensive... all of us.
That sounds like a place for you to get emotional.
No, no, no, I'm glad.
We, even though we're not artists.
Ehhhh.
OK.
I'll take the picture then.
Okay, one, two, three.
Hmm.